Viewers all over the world, I know you are with us.
Whatever medium you are using to view us, I know you are with us.
Distance is not a barrier.
Yes.
I can see you being positioned for healing! (Amen)
I can see you being positioned for deliverance! (Amen)
In the name of Jesus! (Amen)
When one is positioned for healing and deliverance, what else again?
Human hand has no effect again
You have been positioned.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, you have been positioned. (Amen)
You have been positioned. (Amen)
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Once you have been positioned, healing is yours, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Once you have been positioned, deliverance is yours, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Once you have been positioned, blessing is yours, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
In the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Viewers, I can see you being healed, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Check yourself! I can see you being healed, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Thomas, check yourself! In the name of Jesus, be healed! (Amen)
Thomas, check yourself! I can see you being healed, in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Because Thomas wants to know whether he is healed,
"Let me see. Man of God said that I should check myself".
That is Thomas.
Thomas, check yourself! I say you are healed, in the name of Jesus!
A woman who has been on the sickbed,
you can see her getting up saying, "Oh my God! I can walk now!"
Your business can begin to walk, in the name of Jesus!
Your career, begin to walk, in the name of Jesus!
I am seeing a woman right now; she has been on the sickbed for many years.
Right now, she is walking!
What does that mean?
Your business is walking right now, in the name of Jesus!
Your career has begun to walk, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I told you I was looking at a woman
who has been on the sickbed for many years, walking instantly.
What does that mean to you?
It means, your business is walking!
Your career is walking now!
I say, it is walking now!
I say, your career is walking now!
Your career is walking; you should be ready to walk!
Match your actions with your words.
Right now, it is time to match your actions with your words.
When I say, "Your career is walking!", you believe.
Don't say because I said it.
This is what God asked me to tell you.
Your future is walking now!
Your career is walking now!
Your finances are walking!
Your marriage is walking!
Say, "It is walking!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Oh my God! This is a new dawn!
This is a new dawn!
Good Morning!
TT: Mel Flowers 29/07/2018